WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
www.tvsubtitles.net
He's amazing.
Unbelievable.
When did he move to town?
Couple of weeks ago.
Think his name's Brandon.
I hear he's got
the most beautiful cock.
I rolled over and you weren't there.
What are you doing?
Sitting here. Thinking.
Why don't you come back to bed?
I can't sleep.
Ben...
I keep wondering.
Where he is?
And hoping that he's alright.
Yeah, me too.
I keep searching for something -
something that...
..we could have said,
we should have said,
that would've changed his mind.
And have you found it?
What we should have said?
That's because there isn't anything.
He was determined to leave
so he left.
There wasn't anything
we could've done to have stopped him.
Why are you
beating yourself up over it?
Because he was my blood.
You still have a healthy
baby daughter, Michael.
She'll be loved,
sent to a good school,
raised in a world where she'll have
every chance, every opportunity.
Not like Hunter, who had nothing.
Less than nothing.
I wanted to give him
all those things he never had.
So did I.
But I failed.
You didn't fail.
Yes, I did.
I did fail.
We gave him a home,
everything we could've ourselves,
to make him a part of our family.
Then why isn't he still here?
Ahh! Ahhh!
So, did you fuck him over?
Did I ever!
Fucked him over the couch,
over the kitchen counter,
over the coffee table...
Who do you think you are, Theodore?
Me?
Yeah, I have to admit,
I was pretty impressive.
But after you ploughed him
so deep you could plant corn,
that's when you really
gave it to him, right?
Right?
Teddy?
Not yet.
What do you mean, 'not yet'?
Well, why rush it?
It's all so...delicious.
Have you forgotten
what that person did to you?
How he humiliated you?
Aunt Pity Fuck?
Thanks for the memories.
That's why I'm waiting for
exactly the right moment
when the revelation of who I am
will have maximum impact.
Might I interject a word or two?
They say revenge
is a dish best served cold,
but in this particular instance,
it's a dish best served hot
and hard
and as many times as possible.
And you've served it almost
as many times as McDonald's!
Remember your plan, your strategy.
I say screw your courage
to the sticking place.
Better yet, just screw.
I had no idea you were
living under such conditions.
What conditions?
It's a perfectly decent apartment.
'Perfectly decent'
isn't good enough for my daughter.
Well, at the moment,
it's all your daughter can afford.
You didn't have to do all this.
Mmm. Nice stuffed chicken breast
that you like.
Glace cookies.
Oh.
I just don't see
why she has the house.
It was my decision to leave.
But still, it doesn't seem fair.
At the moment, 'fair'
is not a word in my vocabulary.
Darling, I know
we've had our differences,
and you've no idea
how much it hurt me,
but considering
your current situation,
can't we just put all that behind us?
I'd like nothing better.
Good.
Then come live with us.
What?
Your dad and I talked it over
and we think it a splendid idea
if you and Gus were to move in.
At least until you get
your life back together.
I don't think that's
a very good idea, Mom.
But we've plenty of room. And I
promise not to get in your way.
It's not just that.
The last thing you need is
to have a toddler running around.
I can barely keep up myself.
I would love to get
the chance to know him.
So would your father.
As much as I appreciate the offer...
Now, before you say no, just think
of all the money you'll save.
But most of all, we'll have
a chance to be a family again.
Hi! Yes!
Yes! Hey!
Tuna melt for Michael, grilled
cheese and bacon for Sunshine,
and for the queer guy,
a bunless burger.
Just like me.
What?
My producer has informed me
that in the future
when I am on screen
I have no ass,
no dick, no sexuality.
I am, as Brian was
so kind to point out,
a ball-less eunuch -
forgive me, that's redundant -
whose whole purpose in life
is to entertain the white folks.
In fact, I shouldn't even be
called a homosexual.
From now on, you can refer to me
as a homo-ineffectual.
Oh, no.
Oh, yes!
Apparently, Pittsburgh
isn't ready to deal with the fact
that queers aren't only
anatomically correct,
but they actually
use all their parts.
It's not just Pittsburgh.
"Yesterday afternoon,
Family America,
"a conservative-based
citizens action group,
"announced they'd
collected enough signatures
"to have Proposition 14
placed on the ballot
"in the upcoming
state-wide election.
"If passed,
the controversial measure
"could dissolve a broad range of
contracts between same-sex couples."
Those goddamn right-wing fucks!
They're at it again.
It's not enough
they can say no to gay marriage.
Now they're gonna
go after everything?
Come on, Ma. Don't overreact.
"Opponents say Proposition 14
"is one of the most homophobic
pieces of legislation
"in our country's history.
"It would effectively negate
powers of attorney,
"wills, leases, child custody
arrangements, joint bank accounts,
"and health insurance
"granted by companies that recognise
domestic partnerships."
Holy shit! That is everything.
Did I hear someone say
"don't overreact"?
That's what some
other people said once.
Next thing you know they were being
shipped off to the camps.
They can't do this, can they?
They already have in Virginia
and a dozen other states
are trying to do the same.
But if that happens,
it would destroy everything
you and Ben have worked for,
that you've built together.
Tell me about it.
I could lose my health insurance
from Ben's job.
They could invalidate our mortgage.
We could lose the house.
And what about your plans
to adopt Hunter?
You mean if he ever comes back.
Sorry.
It's not just Ben and me.
It's everyone.
It's Mel and Linz and the kids,
Eli and Monty, maybe even you.
Me?
Well, if you and Brian
were to ever...
We won't.
Well, you never know.
Could mellow.
He's not a hardy burgundy, Michael.
He's not going to mellow.
Whatever that proposition
would take away
is something he would never
give me in the first place.
You're not actually considering
going to live with them?
It seems like
a perfectly viable option.
Yeah, so's jumping off a roof.
Alright. Enough.
They're still my family.
Yeah, family that never accepted you
or me or our children.
A family that basically disowned you,
wouldn't speak to you,
wanted nothing to do with you,
and now suddenly they show up
out of the blue to rescue you.
I smell goyim.
It is possible for people to change.
People, yes. Your parents, no.
She said she wants to get to know
her grandson, to make amends.
Uh-huh.
And getting rid of the apartment
will take the pressure off me
and us financially.
Yeah, but is it worth the price?
If they're willing
to admit they were wrong,
change their minds,
learn from their mistakes,
then I owe it to them
to at least consider their offer.
Congratulations, stud.
That's your third time tonight.
And who's keeping score?
I am.
Look at him -
so smug, so self-satisfied.
Now is the perfect time
to send him off
with his not-unattractive tail
between his legs.
What the fuck for?
You've got the sonofabitch where you
want him - with his ass in the air.
And it's not a bad one, I might add.
Don't listen to him. Tell.
What the hell does he know? Fuck!
Would you get off my back?
Huh?
Oh, nothing. You're just, er,
getting a little heavy, that's all.
Oh. Just thought there was something
you wanted to tell me.
Yeah, actually, er...there is.
Go for it, Teddy. Come on.
This is your chance.
You, er...
You wanna go to Babylon
tomorrow night?
Where's your backbone?
Your fortitude?
Where's the lube?
Club was packed tonight.
Hmm, that's nice.
A line all the way around the block.
Great.
Barely any room on the dance floor.
Whatever else happens,
by all means, keep on dancing.
What about you, dear?
How was your evening?
Not nearly as exciting as yours.
I spent it here.
Alone.
Thinking.
And don't say
"Always a dangerous sign."
I made some decisions.
About what?
My life.
Ah.
What I want.
I thought you'd
already worked that out.
You were gonna live off your
considerable Hollywood wealth
and try your hand at being an artist.
Why are you making fun of me?
I'm not making fun.
You're making me
fucking nervous as hell.
Just tell me what you want.
What you've decided.
And we can go to bed and fuck.
You already know what I want.
I've already told you.
That's right. You have.
A husband, a family, a home,
all the things that
make life worth living.
Would you fucking cut it out?
Just stop it.
And I know you can't
give me those things.
Not 'can't'. Can't implies that
I'm incapable. It's that I won't.
I accept that.
I suppose it's why
I've always loved you.
Oh! Oh, the untameable beast.
But to be a couple, both people
have to want the same things.
To move in the same direction.
If they can't or...or won't...
..they really have nowhere to go.
Probably not.
Then why are we still doing this if
we both know it's never gonna work?
Damned if I know.
Where are you going?
Mmm...
I'll figure it out.
Let me know.
Oh, my goodness!
You turned into a monster.
Careful, Ron. Your back.
Hey, partner.
You wanna go see your room?
Would you ladies excuse us gents?
Didn't I tell you he'd be thrilled?
Mom!
What?
You have my prom picture out.
I've always loved that picture.
Look at that hair. That gown.
It's embarrassing.
Not to me.
You know, sometimes I come in here
and I just sit.
You do?
Sometimes I feel
it's all I have left of you.
Thanks, Mom, for being so generous.
It's our pleasure, darling.
By the way, we have some people
coming for dinner tonight.
I mean, nothing formal,
just Al and Lois Seggerman
and someone from Dad's office.
Don't worry. I won't be in the way.
I'll stay up here,
take a bath, read.
I was hoping you'd join us.
It's been a long day and...
I understand. Whatever you like.
But if you change your mind,
Elvira's making your favourite -
salmon and dill sauce.
I told her it was
your welcome home dinner!
Oh, then I suppose I have no choice.
It's so good to have you back.
Reading the dvd titles?
I do that sometimes
to make sure I don't need glasses.
'Singin' in the Rain',
'Some Like it Hot',
'Dirty Harry'.
How'd that get there?
Oh, yeah, I remember.
I thought it was a porn film.
Hey, joking.
ok, it wasn't very funny.
How about you come with me
to Bed, Bath and Beyond?
I'm buying throw pillows for the bed.
'Queer Guy' says
it's a stylish and inexpensive way
to accentuate the colour scheme
and enliven a room.
Of course, we don't need pillows
to enliven a room, do we?
Ben?
I remember watching
those movies with Hunter.
He'd never even heard of
'Singin' in the Rain'.
He loved it.
Must've seen it 95 times.
That was even after he wasn't gay.
Please come with me.
Everything in this house
reminds me of him everywhere I look.
That's why it might be a good idea
to get out for a while.
You know, take your mind
off of things.
Listen, there's a meeting at the Gay
and Lesbian Centre tomorrow night
about this Proposition 14.
So?
So we should go.
They're gonna need volunteers.
Who better than someone as
intelligent, well-informed,
authoritative
and - not to mention - hot as you?
Last thing I want to think about
right now is another gay cause.
It's not just another gay cause.
When we got married, you said
this was just the beginning.
Well, now it looks like
it's the beginning of the end.
Listen, I'm just as upset about this
as you are.
Every time I hear that door open
or the phone ring,
I think it's him.
I just thought it would
make us both feel better
if we got involved in something.
I don't want to
get involved in something, ok?
I don't give a shit about
Proposition 14, or 15 or 16.
All I care about is "Where is he?".
Is he alright?
Am I ever going to see him again?
So let somebody else
sit on that goddamn committee.
I've given enough.
I can't believe he let you walk out
and didn't even try to stop you.
I didn't expect him to.
Well, if either of you had ever
bothered to read Jackie Collins,
you would know that
in the last chapter
the hero finally realises
that he has loved the heroine -
in this case the heroine being you -
all along, and begs her to stay.
That's why it's called fiction.
Fight Proposition 14.
Thanks.
There's a meeting tomorrow
at the centre.
You people need Jesus in your lives.
Yeah, and you need a good blow job.
That is if you can find anyone to
give you one. And don't look at me!
That no-good sonofabitch!
How could he do that to you
after all these years?
He didn't do anything.
I wanted one thing
and he wanted another
and since neither one of us could
give the other what he needed,
we decided it'd be best to move on.
So where are you gonna go?
You could always come back to
Debbie's Boarding House.
Share Emmett's room.
Um, perhaps Emmett would
like to be consulted on that.
Don't worry.
I have it worked out.
I'll stay with Ben and Michael
until I get a place of my own.
A place of your own? At your age?
Deb, I'm not a kid anymore.
You were never a kid.
I know, but you'll
always be a kid to me.
Besides, it's time
I made it on my own.
Like Mary!
And even though I'll miss Brian
and I wish we were still together,
this'll be good for me.
Right?
Right.
Yeah, damn...damn right.
Vote no on Proposition 14.
Yeah, thanks.
No on 14. Meeting at the Centre.
Oh, excuse me, folks.
I gotta go pee again.
Damn prostate.
Al, please!
Oh, don't be embarrassed, honey.
It's not as if I
brought up my haemorrhoids.
What can I say? Al is Al.
I'm afraid I'm a little young
for this crowd.
My prostate's still in working order.
But I'd be glad to show you
my tennis elbow, if you like.
That's ok.
So, you work with my dad?
Going on five years now.
He's a great guy.
And you - you work at
the Sidney Bloom Gallery?
Yes, that's right.
I don't get much time
to go to galleries,
but I did manage to catch
the Sam Auerbach show.
Did you have anything
to do with that?
Actually, I put it together.
Really?
You did a great job.
And the mural down at Penn Plaza
is...it's a knockout.
But, of course, I'm not an expert.
You don't have to be an expert
to know what you like.
I happen to agree with you.
It's bold, larger than life.
Completely unpredictable. Much like the man.
And like the man, best appreciated
from a safe distance.
The old folks
are gonna bore themselves
with pictures from
their Alaskan cruise.
Why don't you two make your escape
and we'll call you for dessert?
ok.
Teddy!
Oh...hi, Em.
Enough with all the greetings
and salutations. I want details.
How'd it go when you told him?
Did he die of shame?
Will I be catering
the memorial service?
Stop with all the questions.
Oh, my God.
What?
It's just what I was afraid of.
I can see it in your eyes.
What are you talking about?
You've fallen for him, haven't you?
Admit it. It's true.
Hey, look, here's Brian.
Brian, buddy, great to see you.
Brian, why are you here?
Why am I here? Hmm.
That's a question that philosophers,
scientists and theologians
have been asking themselves
for thousands of years.
Best I can come up with is
we live in Pittsburgh.
Where the hell else am I gonna go?
I believe Emmett means
we didn't expect to see you,
considering you and Justin broke up.
You must be devastated.
We're so sorry.
Thanks for the sympathies -
another - and the condolences,
but I'm not devastated.
And you're not sorry, so, please,
spare me the sentiments
and the sentimentality.
It's a relief to know
you won't be dying of
a broken heart anytime soon.
Silly us to even think you had one.
I'm doing just fine.
Yeah, we can see.
And I'm sure Justin is too.
Oh, he's doing better than fine.
He's picked himself up,
dusted himself off,
and started all over again.
Glad to hear it.
Be sure and give him my regards
the next time you see him.
Tell him yourself next time
you're over at Michael and Ben's.
He's moved in with them.
Another.
So I said to him, "Wyatt, we're gonna
have to cancel your play date,
"because your friend
can't come over today."
And he said - and I swear -
"Daddy, I can play with
my other friend."
And I said, "What other friend?"
And that's when he showed me.
No!
Oh, yes.
That's what he calls his penis -
his 'friend'.
Oh!
Couldn't believe it. He's five.
Oh, thank God Gus hasn't discovered
his 'friend' yet.
And so when I told my ex,
she got all upset about it,
wanted him to go to a shrink.
And because I thought it was funny,
she thought I should go to a shrink.
And then it turned into
a competition
about who's a better parent,
and now...
I know all about it, believe me.
Would you mind if I stopped by
your gallery some afternoon
and took you to lunch?
That would be great.
What about Thursday?
Thursday's fine.
Although, just to be fair, I think
there's something you should know.
I'm a lesbian.
Oh.
If that's a problem...
Er, no, it's... No, it's not a problem.
It's just not exactly
what your parents told me
when they invited me for dinner.
What exactly did they tell you?
They said that you'd just
broken up...with a man.
Whoo!
Hey, hot guy.
Hey. There you are.
Hmm. I brought some friends.
I want them to meet you.
Well, any friend of yours
is a friend of mine.
Aunt Pity Fuck.
Who's that?
Some freak!
Come on.
Troy.
Oh, hey.
Remember me?
We hooked up a few months ago.
Sure. Right, right, right.
So, uh...how was I?
Hot.
You said you'd call
but I guess you lost my number.
So I'll give it to you again.
Promise not to lose it?
Word of honour.
Fucking losers!
They just don't get it, do they?
These guys, I feel sorry for them.
I can't help it.
It's my nature.
So out of the goodness of my heart,
I have sex with them.
Give them something to remember
for a rainy day.
But it's never enough.
They're pitiful.
Fucking pitiful.
Yeah. I know what you mean.
I was one of them.
What? But you're hot.
Well, you didn't think so then.
Pride? 2002?
I thought there was something
familiar about you.
I was one of your pity fucks.
A fact you made painfully clear.
Well, guess what?
Now you're mine.
And don't look so bewildered.
I sought you out.
I waited for the right moment.
Guess this is it.
You're kidding, right?
Afraid not.
Hey, look at it this way.
You'll always have something
to remember me by.
You're dumping me?
It's a fag-eat-fag world.
Fuck you.
You know...
..I liked you...
..a lot.
I really did.
Jesus Christ. I'm coming!
ok.
ok!
Stop already?!
Brian!
Excellent, Professor.
You recognise the subject
and can identify him by name.
We've gone to bed.
That's right. I forgot.
The Stepford husbands turn in early!
Get in here.
You'll wake the whole neighbourhood.
I want to see your wife.
Where is the little woman?
I mean, little husband.
If you're referring to Michael...
Who the fuck else
would I be referring to?
He's asleep!
Rouse him!
Wake him up.
Michael, you get your ass down here!
Alright. You better go.
I'm not going anywhere.
No. I said you're leaving.
Michael!
Get your ass out of my house.
Ben! It's ok.
I'll handle it. Just go to bed.
You sure?
Well, Mikey...
..congratulations.
For what?!
You won.
To the spoiler goes the victory.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Of course you don't.
No-one plays dewy-eyed innocent
better than you.
Although, at 34,
you're getting a bit
long in the tooth for short pants.
Speaking of outgrowing your act...
..nothing's more pathetic -
to use one of your favourite words -
than an over-the-hill club boy.
You infected him...
..with your petty bourgeois,
mediocre, conformist,
assimilationist life!
Thanks to you, he's got visions -
babies, weddings, white picket fences
dancing in his blond little head.
And you think I put them there?
Before you and your husband
tied the noose around your necks,
he was perfectly happy!
And now he's a defector
just like the rest of you!
He was never perfectly happy!
Waiting for years for you to say
"I love you."
"You're the only one I want."
That's not who I am!
Don't we all know?!
And now he's here in your house...
It's a home.
It's a farce!
It's a freak show!
Call it what you want.
I honestly don't care.
But he didn't leave
because I 'infected' him.
He left because of you.
Who wouldn't?!
Knock, knock.
Just wanted to say goodnight.
Did you enjoy dinner?
The salmon was delicious.
Al and Lois couldn't stop raving
about how wonderful you look.
That's nice.
And Stephen's quite charming,
don't you think?
Yes. Quite.
Goodnight, darling.
Sleep well.
Mum.
Hmm?
Why did you invite him here tonight?
He's your father's associate.
We've been meaning to have him over.
And I thought you might like
having someone to talk to.
That was very thoughtful.
You seemed to be enjoying yourself.
I liked him very much.
I'm very glad to hear it.
But not in that way.
I'm a lesbian, Mother.
You know that.
I thought that was all over with.
All over with?
Your sister told me
you were with a man.
That cunt.
Lindsay.
That happened once
and it was a mistake.
Why was it a mistake?
Perhaps if you'd given it more time,
you might finally have had
a mature relationship.
I've had a mature relationship.
With that person?
Melanie, Mother!
Not "that person".
And, yes, she was my partner
for 10 years.
And that's a helluva lot longer
than any of those three marriages
my darling sister's had.
We have two children together.
You know, that's not immature.
I can't believe I still have to
go through this with you.
I'm sorry, dear.
But it's just not the same.
It isn't.
When I heard about your relations
with a man, I was hoping that...
What?
That I'd be the daughter
you'd always dreamt of?
Well, I'm not, Mum.
And I never will be.
So if that's why you asked me
to come and live here,
then I'm afraid
I've disappointed you...
..once again.
What's up, Bri?
You see that?
How can I miss it?
Well, are you gonna
do anything about it?
The kid's hot.
Attracts guys, sells drinks.
Well, fuck the drinks.
If he wants to get his dick sucked,
he can take his act to the back room.
I'll tell him.
Wait.
Tell him...
..he's barred from the club.
Permanently.
Oh, come on, Bri.
Just do it.
Now!
In a recent Hollywood movie
about the Trojan War,
there was a small
but very significant alteration
in the legend as recounted
by Homer in the 'Iliad'.
Achilles didn't go to war
because the Greeks killed Patroclus,
his cousin.
He went to battle because
they killed Patroclus, his lover.
Excuse me, professor.
But what difference does it make
if they change some old legend?
Like, what else is new?
Because that old legend was rewritten
to omit a very important truth -
that the homophobia
which infects our culture
didn't always exist.
There were once
great and powerful cultures
in which the emotional and sexual
love between two men was accepted,
even among warriors.
Yeah. Good for them,
but what about us?
While we're talking about
the Trojan War,
they're trying to take
our rights away.
I understand your concern
but, right now,
we're here to discuss gay imagery
in mythology and history.
If Proposition 14 passes,
pretty soon WE'LL be history.
He's right.
Yeah.
What a dump.
What's so funny?
You do a fabulous Bette Davis.
Or is it Elizabeth Taylor
doing a fabulous Bette Davis?
I'm not doing a fabulous anybody.
All I know is this is a disgusting
place and you're not living here.
I love it.
Are you crazy?
If I am, I have you and Dad to thank.
It's tiny. It smells like something
you never want to meet died here.
You have to share a bathroom
down the hall with God knows who -
crackheads?
Not to mention you can't go out
into the street after dark.
On the other hand, I can afford it,
it's got great light
and, best of all, it's my own place.
How did I ever
give birth to an artist?
Van Gogh's mother was a washerwoman.
Really?
I made it up.
It's, um...
..quite a comedown
from Brian's place.
You weren't so thrilled
when I moved in there.
No. I guess not.
I just wish that...
I can't believe I'm actually
hearing myself say this.
What?
That you and he could have somehow
managed to work things out.
I know.
Me too.
I mean, it's not as if he repeatedly
and systematically lied to you
or abused you or betrayed you,
like your father did to me.
No, of course not.
He saved my life, he took care of me,
he gave me everything.
It's just we each want
different things.
And neither of you
is willing to change?
That's not love.
That's sacrifice.
Hmm.
He feel asleep
the second his head hit the pillow.
Hmm. He's glad to be back
in his own room, in his own bed.
I don't blame him.
I'm trying to catch up on the world.
I feel like I've been living
on a totally different planet.
Me too.
If you want to say it,
go right ahead.
Those words
will never escape my lips.
Why not?
You were right.
It's funny.
No matter what you know up here...
..you hope against hope...
..in here...
..that your parents, at least,
will love you unconditionally.
We'll try and do better
with our kids.
Where are you going?
To a hotel, I guess.
Thanks for tonight.
Take your coat off.
What?
You're staying here tonight.
Take your coat off.
I don't know if that's a good idea.
Neither do I,
but you're staying anyway.
You sure?
I'll make us tea and grilled cheese
and we'll figure something out, ok?
Another beer.
And another Cosmo and a diet Pepsi.
On me.
Big spender.
What's the occasion?
We're celebrating.
Teddy finally put that prick Troy
in his proper place.
Up a tight butthole?
Out on his ass.
He's no longer Aunt Pity Fuck.
Congratulations, Theodore.
It's a rare man
who'd rather get even than get laid.
Just out of curiosity,
how great was he?
Beyond great.
Amazing.
The best.
You wouldn't happen
to still have his phone number?
What the fuck is your problem?
Your hand's on my stick.
Why did you bar me from your club?
Because I can.
Getting sucked off on the dance floor
is a very serious offence.
Except when it's you.
Membership has its privileges.
I think you threw me out
because you're afraid
I'll get the hottest guys.
I am the hottest guy.
You mean were.
Since when?
Since me.
Even the mightiest
one day must fall.
The king is assassinated,
the lion is torn to shreds.
Oh, Lord, please.
Spare us from wearisome cliches.
Listen...twerp.
You think you get to be the best
by just showing up
and announcing that you are?
You have to prove it first.
I thought I already had.
By picking off a couple of twinks
before I got to them?
You're gonna have to
do better than that.
Then how about we pick?
Say, the 10 hottest guys
we can find.
And the one who
fucks them all first wins.
You know the game.
I also know the outcome.
I admire your confidence.
But they say every star burns its
brightest just before it burns out.
Ooh.
Say you win.
I get into Babylon.
And if you win?
I get into you.
Michael!
We've saved seats.
Hey, honey. Where's Ben?
Um, he had other things to do.
What other things are more important
than this?
Good evening, everyone.
Thank you for coming.
I guess we all know why we're here -
to join in the statewide effort
to defeat Proposition 14.
Yeah.
Whoo!
That's the spirit
we're gonna need in order to win.
Here to help us is one of
the organisers of Stop Prop 14,
Congresswoman Beth Edelstein.
Thank you.
Thanks, Tannis, Philip.
And thank all of you
for coming tonight.
As you know,
our rights as full and equal citizens
of the United States
are being threatened.
Not by outside forces or terrorists
but by our own government,
by religious leaders who in their
effort to strip us of our humanity,
claim that God is on their side,
and by other Americans
acting out of hate and ignorance.
We have got to stop them.
But it's not going to be easy.
"Vote to save America" -
can you believe that's what
they're calling themselves? -
has many supporters
and is well-funded.
Mind if I sign up?
That's why we're going to need
the help of everyone in this room
as well as your families
and your friends
to donate as much time and money
as you can.
Volunteer to serve
on various committees,
make calls, canvass neighbourhoods.
Sign up and fight
as if your future depends on it.
Because it does.
Whoever thought
it'd come to this, huh?
Fighting for, like what she says,
for our lives.
It's what we've always had to do.
Next time
we just have to do it harder.
I'm up for it.
Me too, Sunshine.
'Bye.
'Bye, Ted.
I'm glad you changed your mind.
How come?
"With his eyes fixed firmly in the
past, he failed to see the future.
"So by the present,
he was destroyed."
I guess you're trying to tell me
that if you didn't do anything,
and we lost,
you'd never forgive yourself.
You got it.
Hey.
How was the meeting?
You should have been there.
I'm not Rage.
Saving Gayopolis isn't my thing.
You doing ok?
Yeah, I'm fine.
And you?
Likewise. Thanks for asking.
Well, I guess I better get going.
Me too.
Take care of yourself.
You too.
ok.
See ya.